http://www.freestylephoto.biz/privacy-policy

Newsletters
We're Hiring!
Please Note : ***Due to Covid & the Holidays, please expect shipping delays.***
We will be closed Wednesday through Friday, December 23rd - 25th for the Christmas Holiday and Wednesday through Friday, December 30th - January 1st for the New Year Holiday. Orders placed before noon Pacific Standard Time on the preceding Tuesdays, will ship the same day. Orders placed after Noon Pacific Standard Time on those Tuesdays, will ship on the following Mondays.
Wishing you a Safe and Happy Holiday Season!
Home
>Freestyle Privacy Policy
Information
About Us
Contact Us
Locations & Hours
News
Partners
Freestyle Privacy Policy
Below is Freestyle Photographic Supplies privacy notice. We value the trust and confidence you have in us that we will respect your privacy and handle your information in a responsible manner. By visiting Freestylephoto.biz, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy notice.
Freestyle Photographic Supplies Corporate Headquarters:
5124 Sunset Boulevard
Hollywood, CA 90027
Ph: (323) 660-3460
Fax: (323) 284-0050
Contact: info@freestylephoto.biz
If you have any concerns about our privacy notice, please contact us at the above corporate address, email address, phone or fax numbers.
Personal Information We Collect
The information you provide us helps us personalize and improve your shopping experience.
We store all information that you enter on our Web site. If you choose not to provide certain information, it may inhibit our ability to properly service your needs. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as answering your questions and requests, shipping your products and communicating to you about your order(s) and any special offers that we may have.
There are certain types of information that we store when you visit our site. Like many web sites, we use "cookies" to track information about how you use our site and to make return visits to our site more convenient. The Help button of the toolbar on most browsers can tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies. There are also several companies that offer utilities that will help you to visit Web sites anonymously. It is your right to use these tools while visiting our site. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if you utilize these tools. For example: cookies allow your selected products to remain in your cart for up to 30 days, or until you submit your order. If you clear your cookie cache, you cart will empty. However, a "wishlist" is tied to your account and will remain if cookies are cleared.
Do We Share Information?
The information that you give us remains confidential and is not sold to other companies for any reason, including solicitation. If our policy changes, you will receive notification prior to your information being shared with a third party, and you will have an opportunity to block your information from being released.
Security of Your Information
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using encryption software. This encryption protects information that you input. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card when confirming an order back to you. Please note that we do have to transmit the entire credit card number to the credit card company while processing your order.
Shared Computers
In order to protect your private information when using a shared or public computer, be sure to Log Off of our site when you have finished shopping with us. The Log Off button is located on our home page just above the Search button.
Children
Freestylephoto.biz does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under 18 years of age, you may use Freestylephoto.biz only with the consent of a parent or guardian.
